export const reactData = [
  {
    question: "To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
    Options: ["none",
      "react-native upgrade",
      "both B & D ",
      "react-native init",],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question: "JSX stands for ?",
    Options: ["JavaScript XML",
      "JavaScreenXML",
      "JointScript XML",
      "none",],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question: "________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
    Options: [
      "Redux",
      "Interaction manager",
      "none",
      "stylesheet",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question: " React native was initially released in___",
    Options: [
      '2000',
      '2008',
      '2015',
      '2014',
    ],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question: 'React Hooks are introduced in which React version?',
    Options: ["16.2",
  "16.4",
"16.6",
"16.8",],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1,
  },
  // {
  //   question: 'What is used in ReactJs to increase performance',
  //   Options: ["Both B and c",
  //     "Original DOM",
  //     "Virtual DOM",
  //     "None of the above",
      
  //   ],
  //   correct: 4,
  //   marked: -1,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which of the following is the correct name of React.js?",
  //   Options: [
  //     "React",
  //     "React.js",
  //     "ReactJS",
  //     "All of the above",
  //   ],
  //   correct: 4,
  //   marked: -1,
  // },
  {
    question:
      'How can you create a new React Native project?',
    Options: ["npx create-react-app new-app",
      "npx react-native init new-app",
      "npm create-react-native-app ",
      "expo run new-app",],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which navigation library is commonly used in React Native?",
    Options: ["React Router",
      " React Native Navigation",
      " React Native Router",
      " React Navigation",

    ],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1,
  },
  {
    question:"Which programming language is used in React Native?",
      Options: [
        "java",
        "C#",
        "JavaScript",
        "C++"
      ],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1,
  },
];
